I /G Itallo Gama

S O F T W A R E E N G I N E E R

- (508) 425 9727
- Itallo.gama15@gmail.com
- ♥ Worcester, MA
- LinkedIn Link
- % GitHub Portfolio Link

ABOUT ME

Military Veteran with experience in a variety of leadership, multilingual, troubleshooting, problem resolution and project management skills whom would like to further grow as a software engineer after successful coding school completion.

Software Engineer with a foundation in client facing Sales and Customer services and a passion for learning new skills and technologies. In search for an opportunity that will enable continued growth and further develop my experience as a Software Engineer, where I can create efficient applications, while maintaining user experience.

TECHNICAL

HTML | CSS | Javascript | React | BootStrap | SQL | MongoDB | Vue.js | PSQL | Sequelize | Python | Flask.py | Express | Node.js | MongoDB | Mongoose | SQLAlchemy | AWS₃

STRENGTHS

Detail oriented | Problem solving | Teachable

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

High School Diploma

Abby Kelley Foster High School

May 2012

SERVICE

Team Chief, Private First Class

US Army National Guard

January 2015 - present

EXPERIENCE

Engineering Bootcamp

General Assembly / Boston MA/ July 2021 – October 2021

Developed 5+ full stack application with industry leading web technology and tools

 Practice Agile principles including standups, code reviews and pair programming working collaboratively with 25 fellow developers over GitHub

Relationship Banker

Bank of America / Worcester MA/ November 2020 – July 2021

Provided financial advice by applying financial disciplines in the banking industry while processing transactions on client's accounts.

• Partnered with management to improve operational & sales processes

Command Security Operator

Securitas / Marlborough MA/ January 2019 - May 2020

Monitored multiple areas for potential threats relaying information to fellow officers.

 Managed and mentored other operators to ensure tasks met company standards thru detailed logs of activity and any incident reports

Retail Sales Consultant

AT& T/ Millbury MA/ May 2017 – October 2018

Handled all administration aspects of the sales cycle while maintaining strong knowledge of all products, accessories, pricing plans, promotions and service features.

Business Expert award for Distinguishing Customer Service & Sales

Store Repair Technician

iMobile / Worcester MA/ March 2014 – May 2016

Repaired products by utilizing tools and processes to triage, determining the most effective repair method for each device.

Successfully supported team with client troubleshooting and repair